# OLEG TABACHNIKOW

# Frontend Engineer

Tel Aviv - Jaffa, Israel · +972539240665

#### olegtabachnikow@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/olegtabachnikow

As a highly motivated full-stack developer, my experience covers Israel and United States. I have extensive experience building single page applications and mobile applications with a variety of programming languages. I constantly seek to improve my developer skill set by completing additional courses and staying up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies. In fact, I was even requested to return and teach certain courses due to my proficiency and soft skills.

## **SKILLS**

- Frontend: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, React Native, Ant Design, i18n, Framer Motion, HTML5, CSS3
- Backend: NodeJS, Express, MongoDB
- Tools: Postman, Github, Firebase, Figma, Adobe
- Experience with NoSQL, JSON and REST APIs

#### Languages:

- English Full Professional Proficiency
- Hebrew Basic
- Russian Native

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **JANUARY 2023 – JUNE 2023**

#### FRONTEND ENGINEER, EDEAL INC, USA

- Conceptualized and developed a comprehensive, reusable component library, streamlining the development process and promoting consistent design across projects.
- Developed a two fully functional websites using HTML, CSS, and React to showcase company products/services and enhance online presence.
- Implemented SEO best practices to optimize website and landing page for search engines, resulting in increased organic traffic and improved search rankings.
- Integrated analytics tools (such as Google Analytics) to track website performance, user behavior, and conversion rates, providing valuable insights for data-driven decision-making...

#### **NOVEMBER 2022 - MARCH 2023**

#### FRONTEND ENGINEER, GET ROBO VPN, RUSSIA

 Developed a responsive and user-friendly Single Page Application (SPA) for seamless integration into the Telegram Web App Bot.

#### **MARCH 2022 – AUGUST 2022**

# FRONTEND ENGINEER, AVA MIND, ISRAEL

Assumed a leadership role in strategizing project roadmap, effectively coordinating with key stakeholders to maintain alignment throughout the development process.

# **EDUCATION**

2022

YANDEX PRACTICUM, ISRAEL

2017

**ECONOMICS & ENTERPRISE MANAGEMENT, POLOTSK STATE UNIVERSITY**